<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyShopping Pro</string>

    <string name="favourite_dialog_fragment_button_ok" translatable="false">Ок</string>
    <string name="favourite_dialog_add_note_text_label">Add a note to save as a favorite:</string>
    <string name="dialog_title">"Do you want to add this shop to favorite?"</string>
    <string name="dialog_meaasge">"Are you sure you want to delete? Press: No or Yes " </string>
    <string name="dialog_meaasge_all">"Are you sure you want to clear the entire list? Press: No or Yes " </string>
    <string name="dialog_give_access">Add</string>
    <string name="dialog_decline">No</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="favorites">Favorite</string>
    <string name="history">My wish</string>
    <string name="error">ERROR</string>
    <string name="reload">RELOAD</string>
    <string name="add_to_favorite">To favorite</string>
    <string name="add_to_history">To my wish</string>
    <string name="clear_all">Clear all</string>
    <string name="shops">Shop:  </string>
    <string name="dialog_positiv">Yes</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_clear_all">"Cleaning all... !"</string>
    <string name="add_to_save">"SAVE !"</string>

    <string-array name="goods">
        <item>Appliances</item>
        <item>Computers and electronics</item>
        <item>Smartphones and phones</item>
        <item>Construction and renovation</item>
        <item>Design and decor</item>
        <item>Garden and vegetable garden</item>
        <item>Furniture</item>
        <item>Household products</item>
        <item>Office supplies</item>
        <item>Clothes</item>
        <item>Shoes</item>
        <item>Underwear</item>
        <item>Baby products</item>
        <item>Children\'s clothing and footwear</item>
        <item>Children\'s toys</item>
        <item>Clocks</item>
        <item>Books</item>
        <item>Universal</item>
        <item>Food</item>
        <item>Coffee, tea</item>
        <item>Sports goods</item>
        <item>Gifts</item>
        <item>Flowers</item>
        <item>Everything for the holiday</item>
        <item>Cosmetics and perfumes</item>
        <item>Jewelry</item>
        <item>Bijouterie</item>
        <item>Rest and tourism</item>
        <item>Hunting and fishing</item>
        <item>Interest and hobbies</item>
        <item>Health Products</item>
        <item>Online pharmacies</item>
        <item>Auto products</item>
        <item>Auto Parts</item>
        <item>Tires and wheels</item>
        <item>Climate equipment</item>
        <item>Crockery</item>
        <item>Bags, briefcases, wallets</item>
        <item>Pet supplies</item>
        <item>Miscellaneous</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="id_1">Internet store of household appliances 590.ua – sale of high-quality household appliances of the best brands."</string>
    <string name="id_2">"Comfy is an online store of home appliances and electronics. Here you can buy household appliances and electronics, mobile phones, TVs, laptops, computers, washing machines, refrigerators and many other goods."</string>
    <string name="id_3">"In the Vencon online store, you can choose and buy a split-system air conditioner,  a gas or electric boiler, ventilation equipment, filters for drinking and domestic water, air purifiers and much more. Vencon offers the widest range of modern household appliances and appliances."</string>
    <string name="id_4">"MOYO online store - laptops, phones, household appliances, clothes, household goods. Credit, guarantee, consultation of experts, delivery across Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_5">"Q-Techno is an online store in Ukraine that has been importing new, high-quality, certified products at affordable prices for more than a year. The catalog has a large assortment of goods of various categories. Discounts, promotions, installment plans, gifts, and free shipping are available for many products."</string>
    <string name="id_6">"STYLUS has existed on the Ukrainian online sales market since 2008 and during this time managed to establish itself as a reliable online store. Today, STYLUS offers a wide range of digital equipment, small and large household appliances, books, goods for children."</string>
    <string name="id_7">ROZETKA is the most popular online store in Ukraine, the largest online hypermarket in Ukraine. In the online store ROZETKA you can buy electronics, clothes and shoes, household appliances, auto products, goods for home and business, and many many other goods. Favorable prices and discounts. Official guarantee.</string>
    <string name="id_8">"Eldorado - online store of household appliances and electronics. Eldorado, like many similar stores, started with the sale of electronics and household appliances, and is now one of the largest stores where you can buy absolutely everything for home and recreation at affordable prices."</string>
    <string name="id_9">"Foxtrot is a chain of large and small household appliances stores throughout Ukraine. The stores offer a wide selection of products, the best product taking into account the requirements and financial capabilities of the buyer."</string>
    <string name="id_10">"In the Epicentr online store, you can buy a large assortment of products online: for the garden and vegetable garden, building materials, sanitary ware, furniture, tools, household appliances, electronics, children's goods, sporting goods, dishes and household chemicals."</string>
    <string name="id_11">"Telemart online store is a store of PC components, gaming peripherals and equipment."</string>
    <string name="id_12">"The Venbud building materials store offers a variety of products from proven manufacturers, which are sold with an official warranty. More than 5,000 items on the site are available at reasonable prices with delivery in Kyiv on the day of placing the order or the next day."</string>
    <string name="id_13">"The store provides a large selection of chandeliers, lamps, electrical equipment with delivery in Kyiv and Ukraine. There is a profitable discount program. Website with a unique design bulb.com.ua"</string>
    <string name="id_14">"Арт-Обои - photo wallpapers on the wall to order in just 2 days. Huge catalog of images, designer services. Possibility of payment after delivery."</string>
    <string name="id_15">"An online store that sells handmade icons. Our resource has already satisfied more than 1000 customers who were satisfied with the cooperation. Come in and pick up a beautiful icon for yourself."</string>
    <string name="id_16">"The showroom of fabrics for curtains Niltex.com.ua is located in Kyiv, near the station. Metro Vokzalnaya. The largest selection of fabrics for curtains at the prices of the online store. Possibility to order the production of curtains, home textiles, roller blinds, Roman blinds, purchase the necessary accessories for curtains."</string>
    <string name="id_17">"The company «Мир пола и Декора» specializes in the sale of floor coverings, wallpaper for walls, stucco decoration and curtains from "economy" class to "luxury". Services for your convenience: selection of material, measurement and calculation of the required quantity, delivery, as well as the entire installation process."</string>
    <string name="id_18">"Online store of goods for growing early vegetables. Shading mesh, agrofibre, greenhouse film and much more - wholesale and retail from 1 meter."</string>
    <string name="id_19">"The online store «С Торгом» is one of the largest players in the market for the sale of garden equipment, hand and power tools, construction equipment, machine tools and electric vehicles."</string>
    <string name="id_20">"GreenMarket online store (GrinMarket) is an online store of seedlings - ordering rose seedlings, lily bulbs. Buy seedlings: roses, lilies, grapes, raspberries, currants."</string>
    <string name="id_21">"Buy seeds by mail of vegetables and flowers in Ukraine. We offer a wide range of vegetable and flower seeds. The store cooperates with the largest seed producers from Italy, Germany, France, USA, Holland, Japan, and seeds from Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_22">"In the online store of seeds "Огород" you can comfortably buy goods for your garden, garden, cottage. Currently, the store offers more than 2,000 items of goods for summer residents and gardeners, from the categories: vegetable seeds, flower seeds, seeds of medicinal plants, seeds of rare plants, seeds of the best varieties and hybrids, seeds of annual flowers, seeds of perennial flowers, seeds trees and shrub seeds, dry mycelium of fungi, as well as various plant protection products: fungicides, insecticides, herbicides, seed disinfectants, rodenticides, and of course various fertilizers: for flowers, for vegetables, universal fertilizers and stimulants, plant growth regulators."</string>
    <string name="id_23">"Florium - online store of planting material: sale of plants, buy garden plants, bulbs and seeds by mail with delivery in Ukraine. Sale of plants from Holland. Large database of flowers, seeds, indoor plants and seedlings. Delivery to any city of Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_24">"Online store in-green - one of the largest campaigns for the sale of garden equipment, hand and power tools, construction equipment, electric vehicles and other household goods"</string>
    <string name="id_25">"The online furniture store "Дубок" sells furniture in Rivne and Ukraine. We offer you to buy furniture from the best furniture factories in Lviv, Ternopil, Kyiv, Lutsk, Zhytomyr, Vinnytsia, Donetsk, Zaporizhzhia, Kharkiv, etc."</string>
    <string name="id_26">"Domoteka online furniture and home goods store offers kitchen tables, kitchen chairs, rattan kitchen furniture, acrylic bathtubs, children's sofas and beds."</string>
    <string name="id_27">"Furniture online store "Шопомаг" offers a wide range of furniture products: office furniture, bedrooms, children's furniture, cabaret furniture, upholstered furniture, dining group, mattresses, kitchens."</string>
    <string name="id_28">"«Мебель-Бум» is an online store of furniture and interior items, where you can buy furniture for home and office with delivery in Kyiv and all Ukraine. Here you can buy tables and chairs, beds, bedrooms, sofas, furniture for the living room and kitchen, a wardrobe or a nursery, and you can also order any custom-made cabinet furniture according to an individual project."</string>
    <string name="id_29">"In the online store «Файні Меблі» you will find a large assortment of Ukrainian furniture at the manufacturer's prices. "Fine Furniture" is ready-made furniture from the warehouse as well as to order. The store offers: upholstered and solid furniture, children's furniture, office furniture and much more."</string>
    <string name="id_30">"«Мебельная Планета» is an online furniture store that offers a large catalog of Italian furniture. Exclusive furniture from Italy to order is sure to decorate any living room or bedroom."</string>
    <string name="id_31">"Online furniture store MaxMebel offers high-quality furniture in a large assortment: walls in the hall, bedroom, kitchen furniture, children's walls and bedrooms, chests of drawers, hallway furniture, wardrobes, office furniture, tables."</string>
    <string name="id_32">"«Подушка» online store is pleased to offer its customers a wide range of textiles and household goods - blankets, pillows, bed linen, bedspreads, blankets and many, many other irreplaceable things that will help create home comfort."</string>
    <string name="id_33">"Online store of lamps Lampa.ua - more than 14,000 types of lamps and chandeliers. Opportunity to buy lamps with free delivery to your city: chandeliers, lamps, floor lamps, sconces, table lamps and more. Delivery of lamps is carried out throughout Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_34">"Ecoshop «Экоист» - ecological online store of eco-goods, where you can buy eco goods and eco products, energy-efficient technologies and autonomous systems."</string>
    <string name="id_35">"«Хоздом» - an online store of household goods, household goods: dishes, appliances, household goods, for the bathroom, for the bedroom."</string>
    <string name="id_36">"Sale of various interior items - decorative animal skins, fur bedspreads, sheep and cow skin carpets, stuffed animals and birds, sheep wool bedding and many other exclusive products."</string>
    <string name="id_37">"The internet-shop of lamps "Elekomp.com.ua" sells both in batches and in distribution lighting the products of by-button and industrial recognition of leading European virobniki. In the catalog of the online store elekomp.com.ua, there are: suspended chandeliers, wall chandeliers, chandeliers, chandeliers, lamps, floor lamps, sconces, a majestic selection of accessories and fittings."</string>
    <string name="id_38">"Online store of home textiles, everything for relaxation, comfort and sports. Fast delivery, guarantee, any payment. Blankets, pillows, towels, linens and more."</string>
    <string name="id_39">"Dormeo products are orthopedic and anatomical mattresses, blankets and pillows."</string>
    <string name="id_40">"Laluna - online store for women's clothing, underwear. The store also stocks US Polo Assn women's terry bathrobes, towels, linens and blankets. Leather handbags, briefcases, business card holders and key holders. Delivery across Kyiv and all Ukraine. Cumulative discounts"</string>
    <string name="id_41">"Here you can buy fashionable and stylish clothes, shoes (and not only!) for men and women at affordable prices. Please note that when choosing any product, you can see detailed REAL PHOTO, as well as a dimensional grid of this product. Also, on request - MANUAL measurements. Therefore, you can be 100% sure that you will receive exactly the model that you see in our store."</string>
    <string name="id_42">"«Марафон» is a network of clothing, footwear and accessories stores for outdoor activities and everyday life, a sportswear store. The site presents a wide range of products for outdoor activities, sports and everyday life, well-known world brands Northland, Jack Wolfskin, Columbia, Hi-Tec, Billabong, Merrell, CAT, Briko, Cebe, Reef, Merrell, ski clothing."</string>
    <string name="id_43">"Online store "Mamacity" - clothes for pregnant women and nursing. Our store is designed for pregnant and lactating mothers. Stylish, comfortable clothes, underwear, tights, goods for babies - slings, backpacks. Only high-quality products made from natural fabrics, only the latest models, designed taking into account fashion trends and the requirements of maximum wearing comfort. Goods of Ukrainian, Russian, German, Turkish manufacturers. When buying 2 items, a 3% discount, then there is a system of cumulative discounts! Delivery in Kyiv and Ukraine"</string>
    <string name="id_44">"MODOZA.com - online store of Italian clothes, shoes and accessories. Bags and expensive jewelry. Free shipping and fitting."</string>
    <string name="id_45">"Online store "Остров" is only legendary brands, quality assurance, experienced consultants and convenient delivery."</string>
    <string name="id_46">"Fashionable, high-quality, stylish clothes, shoes and accessories from world brands at an affordable price. Fast delivery in the cities of Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_47">"Online clothing stores from Ukrainian designers in Kyiv. Fashionable and branded clothes in Kyiv. Be fashionable and stylish!"</string>
    <string name="id_48">"The Sniker.ua shoe store offers to buy shoes online in Kyiv, Kharkov, Donetsk, Zaporozhye, Odessa and other cities with delivery throughout Ukraine and the CIS countries."</string>
    <string name="id_49">"Retail men's and women's shoes at wholesale prices. Instant dispatch by "Nova Poshta" or self-delivery, fitting in Dnepropetrovsk - Lenin Square, 1."</string>
    <string name="id_50">"In the Nubuck online shoe store you can buy high-quality men's and women's shoes with free delivery anywhere in Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_51">"Online store of shoes made of genuine leather. The Midashop online store is the leader in footwear sales and unites 10 retail outlets in Kharkov. The Midashop online shoe store will surprise you with a large selection of men's, women's and children's shoes designed for all seasons."</string>
    <string name="id_52">"PUMA.com is the official website and online store of famous Puma sports and fashion clothes and shoes in Ukraine. PUMA.ua - a wide range of products on the site, regular discounts and sales, payment for purchases upon receipt or prepayment."</string>
    <string name="id_53">"Kedoff.Net - online store of branded shoes. Here you can buy high-quality and original shoes at reasonable prices. Delivery in Kyiv and across Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_54">"Ukrainian brand vzuttya - NV Brand. In the assortment of the brand there are people and women, as well as accessories of premium materials."</string>
    <string name="id_55">"Raspashonka.ua - online store for children's goods. Delivery across all Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_56">"All-Ukrainian children's online store Disney offers to buy children's goods at the best prices. The store catalog includes: electric cars, desks, swimming pools, bicycles, strollers, gyro scooters, children's wheelchairs, velomobiles, high chairs, playpens, walkers, swings, car seats, slides, children's balance bikes, play centers, cribs, toys, children's pools."</string>
    <string name="id_57">"Pampik.com - online store for children's goods in Ukraine. Rampik is a store for pregnant women and young parents. Pampik.com is an opportunity to purchase all the necessary baby care products without wasting time shopping."</string>
    <string name="id_58">"Chicco Ukraine - online store: strollers, toys, car seats, high chairs."</string>
    <string name="id_59">"Online store of children's goods eBabyDay. In our assortment: baby strollers, cribs, playpens, car seats, bedding sets, toys, walkers, bicycles, high chairs, deck chairs and more. Free delivery across Lutsk. Each buyer is a gift."</string>
    <string name="id_60">"If you are a caring and loving parent and want to give your baby everything they need and even more, check out Shop-mamka. Here you can purchase high-quality accessories for a comfortable stay and the proper development of your crumbs. Popular European brands and Ukrainian prices will please you!"</string>
    <string name="id_61">"BABYSHOP.UA - Children's online store in Kyiv and Ukraine. BABYSHOP.UA - Official Babyshop online store. Official distributor of Chicco, Munchkin, Molo, Name it, Bogs. Babyshop.ua is a WOW-shop with WOW-brands for future parents and children up to 16 years old. Our WOW brands: Chicco (Italy), Name It (Denmark), Molo (Denmark), Munchkin (USA), Trunki (UK), Stokke (Norway), Bogs (USA), Appaman (USA), Angels Face (UK) ), Point6 (USA)."</string>
    <string name="id_62">"Lolo.com.ua - online supermarket of children's toys and children's goods. Lolo.com.ua is everything you need for your baby and mom! The Lolo online supermarket offers a wide range of children's goods and toys: car seats, children's furniture, bedding sets, mattresses, pillows, blankets, baby carriages, children's transport, bicycles, scooters, electric cars, balance bikes, products for hygiene and baby care, products for mom. Offline stores in Chernihiv. Online store Lolo.com.ua delivers throughout Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_63">"Online store for children's goods "Малышам" - clothes and other goods for babies. In the online store malisham.kiev.ua you can buy high-quality clothes for newborns. Fast delivery in Kyiv and Ukraine! There is a large selection of clothes for newborns: diapers, blankets, undershirts, baby bedding, crawlers, blouses for newborns, baby hats, overalls, envelopes and many other goods."</string>
    <string name="id_64">"Children's clothes from TM Be easy are high-quality, practical and comfortable clothes for everyday wear. Bright prints, comfortable patterns, high-quality materials and accessories will satisfy not only kids but also their parents. Product care is minimal, because the Teflon fabric coating (Dupont certificate) protects the fabric surface from water and dirt."</string>
    <string name="id_65">"Online children's clothing store will help turn the purchase of clothes into a real pleasure and please your child with new clothes without even leaving home with him. The assortment of our store includes children's clothing of the brands MONE, Girandola, Tiffossi."</string>
    <string name="id_66">"Babyart - children's knitwear Komsomolsk at a bargain price. Products at low prices from the manufacturer Komsomolsk. Permanent discounts and promotions. BabyArt.ua is the best children's clothing store in Ukraine for boys, girls and newborns. High quality and environmental friendliness of all products. The store has a wide range of clothes for girls, clothes for newborns, clothes for boys."</string>
    <string name="id_67">"Online store of high-quality children's clothing from the USA and Europe. Carters, OshKosh, SkipHop, H&amp;M and other brands."</string>
    <string name="id_68">"Online store Garnamama.com - clothing for the whole family - children's clothing, women's clothing, men's clothing at an affordable price. Large selection, promotions and discounts. Convenient delivery across Kyiv and Ukraine. Easy exchange/return."</string>
    <string name="id_69">"The online store offers quality children's clothes in a wide range of brands KIKO, Donilo, Carters, Laura Ashley, Calvin Klein, Next, Rocawear, Chicco, Demar, Little Blue Lamb, Scorpian, Benetton, Hello Kitty, Bebekko, Gemboree, Bobitto kids and etc."</string>
    <string name="id_70">"If you are looking for where you can dress your child well, quickly, and most importantly inexpensively, then you are in the right place. Our online children's clothing store KidsTime is pleased to offer you the best for your children at attractive prices."</string>
    <string name="id_71">"Designers LEGO (Lego) wholesale and retail from a dealer in the online store Constructors.com.ua."</string>
    <string name="id_72">"«Профи Тойс» online store is a unique site where all possible toy special equipment is collected for children. Toys from the most famous European manufacturers, the quality is at the highest level."</string>
    <string name="id_73">"Children's electric cars. «Эмобили» online store. Children's jeeps RAV4, Hummer, ATVs, motorcycles, cars. For children from 1–15 years old. A very large selection, low prices and delivery throughout Ukraine. In Kyiv – for free. Best design and quality guaranteed."</string>
    <string name="id_74">"RC helicopters and RC toys. The AmigoToy online store offers a wide range of RC toys such as RC helicopters and cars. As well as souvenirs, handgams, powerballs and neocubes. Large selection at great prices."</string>
    <string name="id_75">"The online store of developing children's toys "Ивашка" offers to buy smart toys for your baby in the widest range at reasonable prices. A variety of educational toys, talking posters, wooden knockers, wooden laces, developing children's rugs, wooden toys, developing children's centers, and many other educational games for children from the most famous manufacturers in the world at the best prices."</string>
    <string name="id_76">"In the online store of children's goods and toys GoodtoyS.com.ua you will be helped to choose the best children's toys according to your criteria."</string>
    <string name="id_77">"The online store of children's toys and goods joykids.kiev.ua provides you with the widest selection of children's toys and related products."</string>
    <string name="id_78">"Our products are high-quality replicas of watches, phones, accessories from world-famous manufacturers, made in Switzerland, Belgium, Austria, and the United Arab Emirates in full compliance with the production technology of original products. Our watches are powered by original Japanese and Swiss movements (ETA, Miyota, ISA, Ronda, Orient, Citizen, Seico, etc.)."</string>
    <string name="id_79">"TakeTime is a rapidly growing online store selling watches. We have a variety of brands and models, among which you can find what you like. Every day the assortment is replenished with new models. By purchasing watches from us, you can be 100% sure of the quality of the goods."</string>
    <string name="id_80">"Online watch store 24K.UA offers a wide range of wrist, mantel, table clocks and alarm clocks. Moreover, 24k.ua is an online store of accessories, gifts, household goods and tourism. 24k.ua is the best online store for gifts, accessories and jewelry. A huge selection of accessories and jewelry from world brands. The best prices in Kyiv. Delivery across all Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_81">"The SWISS-TIME online store is engaged in the retail sale of original Swiss watches. All watches are delivered in original branded packaging with appropriate certificates. We are official dealers in Ukraine of such watch brands: Charmex, Hamiton, Mido, Louis Erard, TISSOT, Grovana, Cover, Appella, Adriatica, Bulova, Certina, Eberhard, Roamer, Swatch, Swiss Military, Fortis, Emporio Armani, Medana, Seiko, DKNY, Diesel, Fossil, Esprit."</string>
    <string name="id_82">"A person of any age, wealth and social status can choose Swiss, Japanese, French, Italian watches in the Ontime.watch online store. Among the huge number of models of the brands Appella and Adriatica, Tissot and Ernest Borel, Casio and Orient, Le Chic and Sauvage, Pierre Ricaud and other world brands, both a teenager and a respectable man can find a suitable men's or women's watch."</string>
    <string name="id_83">"Official distributor in Ukraine of Tissot Swiss watches as well as Diesel, Fossil, Esprit, DKNY, Armani. The main activity of the Vector D company is wholesale sales of watches, bijouterie and jewelry throughout Ukraine, retail trade in its own network of company stores, certified watch service and an online store."</string>
    <string name="id_84">Online watch store Watch4you, Kharkiv. Original swiss and japanese watches.</string>
    <string name="id_85">"In the store you will find any product for sports that you have only heard of. We work directly with all well-known suppliers of simulators from around the world. Warranty and quality."</string>
    <string name="id_86">"Terrasport: sporting goods, sports goods, sporting goods."</string>
    <string name="id_87">"Huge selection of sporting goods at affordable prices. We carry out delivery throughout Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_88">"Sports goods: equipment for martial arts (boxers, wrestling shoes, boxing gloves, kimonos), fitness products, sports equipment. Goods for tourism and fishing. Sale of all kinds of goods for karate, boxing, weightlifting, wrestling, team sports. In the Viasport store, everyone can choose and buy a treadmill, orbitrek, dumbbells."</string>
    <string name="id_89">"Online store of sports, stylish clothes, shoes and accessories adidas - adiTIME. Large selection of sportswear and stylish adidas shoes with delivery in Kyiv and Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_90">"«Протеин» - online store of sports nutrition. Buy sports nutrition from global manufacturers with delivery throughout Ukraine. We have affordable prices and excellent quality. Get stronger with us!"</string>
    <string name="id_91">"DomSporta - online store of sports equipment: professional, for home, power, elliptical. A wide range of exercise equipment with free delivery across Ukraine, warranty, best prices."</string>
    <string name="id_92">"The SportUA online store has been operating on the Ukrainian market since 2009 and represents the following trademarks: ASICS, Errea, Mikasa. Only we present to your attention the widest range of sports products for all sports: clothes, shoes, balls and accessories. By purchasing goods from us, you get only original high-quality products of world famous brands. All goods come only through official representatives of these trademarks in Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_93">"For gifts - a gift shop in Kyiv. To your attention gifts for men and women, original gifts, New Year's gifts, wedding gifts, business gifts, gifts for children, gifts for an anniversary, souvenirs. To give is to please, and a gift is a joy for everyone: who gives and to whom they give, the main thing is to choose it with love, then you will definitely like it. In the online gift shop "Za Gifts" the most interesting and original gifts are selected in the most careful way."</string>
    <string name="id_94">"Creative, stylish and original things in the online store «Мир Подарка»."</string>
    <string name="id_95">"The Gamesua store sells video games, accessories for game consoles. Bearbrick and Kaws figurines. The range is very large and is constantly expanding. There is a repair of game consoles!"</string>
    <string name="id_96">"Online gift shop #1 in Ukraine. All souvenirs and gifts for women and men for any occasion in one place!"</string>
    <string name="id_97">"Online store of oriental souvenirs from Japan and Korea"</string>
    <string name="id_98">"Gift and souvenir shop kaktus.ua offers original (cool, interesting) gifts and souvenirs."</string>
    <string name="id_99">"Everything you can give in one online store. Souvenirs and gifts for men and women, friends and boss."</string>
    <string name="id_100">"«Презента» - gifts with a high reputation. Online gift shop Prezenta - these are elite, prestigious and exclusive expensive VIP gifts."</string>
    <string name="id_101">"The official website of the Ukrainian manufacturer of leather products - BlankNote. Designer bags, handmade travel cases. Women's and men's wallets and wallets made of genuine leather. Gift sets of accessories. Delivery throughout Ukraine!"</string>
    <string name="id_102">"4party.ua - online store of festive goods and carnival paraphernalia. In the store you will find everything you need for Birthday, Theme Parties, New Year, Halloween, March 8 and other holidays. Decorations, table setting elements, carnival costumes and accessories, balloons, souvenirs, gifts, games and entertainment. The All for the Holiday store offers a huge range of popular holiday items for children and adults."</string>
    <string name="id_103">"Internet shop of gifts and jokes. Goods for holidays, anniversaries, parties. Delivery across Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_104">"The store from the manufacturer of Christmas goods Rizdvo.ua offers to buy artificial Christmas trees and pine trees with delivery throughout Ukraine. Factory Рiздво (Rizdvo.ua) - New Year's goods from the manufacturer. rizdvo.ua is the official retail website of the «Різдво» Factory trademark."</string>
    <string name="id_105">"TIMESTAR - artificial Christmas trees at manufacturer's price. In the timestar.com.ua online store you can buy beautiful and high-quality artificial Christmas trees with delivery throughout Ukraine. There is a wide selection of artificial Christmas trees and pine trees for every taste. Also in the TIMESTAR store you can buy a variety of New Year's paraphernalia: electric garlands, Christmas tree garlands, various decorations, New Year's amulets, photo frames and much more. In the timestar.com.ua online store you can find everything to create the atmosphere of the New Year in your home or office."</string>
    <string name="id_106">"The network of stores «Весёлая затея» offers a wide range of gifts, decorations with balls for the holiday. All for the party. Decoration with balloons. Balloon printing. More than a thousand items are always available for you at the most affordable prices and in any quantity."</string>
    <string name="id_107">"CosmeticShop - online store of professional cosmetics. In the store you can buy original cosmetics from the USA, Western Europe, Israel of world famous brands CHI, Biosilk, Goldwell Colorance, Elumen, Topchic, Agadir, AHAVA, e.l.f., Jordana, Philip Kingsley, Orofluido, Dermalogica, NYX, La Femme and others."</string>
    <string name="id_108">"Online store of professional and decorative cosmetics, perfumery and care cosmetics. Huge range, best prices. Perfumes and cosmetics are delivered absolutely free of charge throughout Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_109">"The Profistyle store offers a wide range of high-quality premium cosmetics with delivery throughout Ukraine. Profistyle" is an online store of professional cosmetics for hair, face and body. Here you can buy professional cosmetics with delivery throughout Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_110">"The Eau De Parfum online store offers its customers a wide selection of luxury perfumes from all the world's famous designers at wholesale prices at retail. For regular customers there is a cumulative system of DISCOUNTS and FREE SHIPPING. We are always happy to help you choose your favorite fragrance!"</string>
    <string name="id_111">"The store sells exclusively original perfumes and cosmetics. You will find a wide range of perfumes and cosmetics, niche fragrances, perfume gift sets, vintage and rare perfumes."</string>
    <string name="id_112">"In the online store you can buy professional hair cosmetics Loreal Professional, Paul Mitchell, Matrix, Kerastase with delivery in Kyiv and Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_113">"Bomond.com.ua - official online store of original perfumes and cosmetics of the BOMOND company. The store presents products of global brands Chanel, Dior, Guerlain, Estee Lauder, Lancome, YSL, Sisley, Bobbi Brown, La Mer, Max Factor, L'Oreal, Maybelline and others."</string>
    <string name="id_114">"Lambre is a perfumery and cosmetics from France. Official warehouse in Ukraine. Subscription of consultants with 40% discount."</string>
    <string name="id_115">"Watsons.ua - online store of goods for beauty and health. Watsons.ua (Watsons Ukraine) is high-quality European goods, special offers and promotions, a profitable bonus savings program, delivery throughout Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_116">"EVA.UA - online store of goods for beauty and care. EVA.UA is a modern store for convenient online shopping, a simple and understandable website interface, original products, a large assortment, loyal prices, delivery within Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_117">"Zlato online store - jewelry, jewelry, gold and silver jewelry, rings, earrings, pendants, bracelets, chains, accessories, watches, gifts."</string>
    <string name="id_118">"«Золотий стандарт» is a store that is known not only for a wide range of exquisite, original jewelry, but also presents jewelry made from noble, high-quality metals."</string>
    <string name="id_119">"Jewelry online store AURUM.IN.UA - jewelry at a low price. Guarantee. High quality. Jewelry company "AURUM" provides high quality service and a high level of service."</string>
    <string name="id_120">"Gold.ua is a new generation jewelry online store. Exquisite jewelry made of gold and silver at affordable prices."</string>
    <string name="id_121">"Online store «Золотой Век» - gold, jewelry - a network of jewelry stores."</string>
    <string name="id_122">"Jewelry online store «Укрзолото». Jewelry, earrings, rings, diamonds and more. «Укрзолото» is one of the largest chains of jewelry stores in Ukraine. Affordable prices, fast delivery, installment and credit."</string>
    <string name="id_123">"In the SOVA Jewels online store you can buy gold jewelry, jewelry and gold jewelry. Great prices. Manufacturer."</string>
    <string name="id_124">"ZARINA jewelry house is an online jewelry and jewelry store. Zarina Jewelry House - gold and silver jewelry, jewelry. ZARINA Jewelry House offers a wide selection of gold and silver products - unique collections of diamond rings, earrings, pendants, necklaces made in the style of fashionable classics. The best quality. Delivery throughout Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_125">"INTEX-SHOP.com.ua - online store of INTEX products. The online store offers inflatable beds and mattresses, inflatable pools and INTEX accessories. In the product catalog of the Intex-Shop online store you will find: inflatable pools, frame pools, children's pools, air mattresses, air beds, inflatable boats, game centers, pumps and accessories for pools, inflatable sofas and chairs, sets for swimming, accessories for recreation on the water."</string>
    <string name="id_126">"Trofey.ua - fishing goods store. Inexpensive goods for fishing (fishing goods) with delivery in Ukraine. Product categories: rods, reels, fishing lines and cords, baits, floats and signaling devices, hooks, equipment, baits and nozzles, transportation and storage, accessories, inflatable boats and motors, winter fishing, clothing and equipment, equipment and tourism. Fishing shop Trofey.ua - profitable purchases with a personal discount and promotional codes without leaving home, without traffic jams and queues."</string>
    <string name="id_127">"Online store kapitan.ua offers goods for recreation on the water and on the shore."</string>
    <string name="id_128">"«Апарат»: solution for active fishing, navigation, watering and fishing. Aparat.ua - online store of navigation and portable equipment. A wide range of gps-navigators, fish finders, action cameras, binoculars, autoelectronics, video recorders, radars, car seats, accessories for tourist equipment, goods for fishing and fishing. Quality assurance. Available prices. Shvidka delivery in all regions of Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_129">"Online store 070 offers LED flashlights, lasers, sights, target designators, chargers and batteries, folding knives, as well as many accessories for tourism and expeditions."</string>
    <string name="id_130">"Travel online store X-ZONE offers goods for recreation and tourism, travel equipment."</string>
    <string name="id_131">"In the store you will find everything for sports, tourism, mountaineering and just outdoor activities. Equipment and clothing for tourism, extreme sports and outdoor activities. Professional advice to active athletes."</string>
    <string name="id_132">"Tents, backpacks, sleeping bags from Normal companies, Equipment, Gronell hiking shoes, thermal underwear, gas cylinders, burners, hiking clothes."</string>
    <string name="id_133">"Militarka.com.ua - military trade online store that specializes in military equipment. Here you can find and purchase authentic original things of the former Soviet Army, modern uniforms of the Ukrainian soldier."</string>
    <string name="id_134">"Everything for fishing in the online store www.mirrybolova.com.ua. Large assortment, best price guarantee, experienced consultants, discount program."</string>
    <string name="id_135">"Fishing online store profish.ua - the best choice of goods for fishing in Ukraine. In the profish.ua online store you can buy fishing products at the best prices with delivery in Ukraine to Kyiv, Kharkov, Lviv, Dnipro, Odessa. Everything you need for fishing: tackle and equipment for carp, spinning, float and bottom, winter fishing, clothes and shoes, food and baits, boats, tents, etc., all new items and exclusive positions - all this is available in the PROFISH fishing store ."</string>
    <string name="id_136">"The online store Nitecore-ua.com, as an official representative of the American company Nitecore, offers to buy original flashlights for hunting and tourism throughout Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_137">"The FishingStock online store offers the most modern fishing tackle, spinning rods and other fishing products at an affordable price."</string>
    <string name="id_138">"«FISH-FISH» - online store of fishing goods. Large selection of Japanese wobblers deps, evergreen, fishycat, megabass, ima, reins, o.s.p, tiemco, vagabond, as well as spinning rods, reels, silicone lures, rods, cords, lines. Sale from own wholesale warehouse without intermediaries."</string>
    <string name="id_139">"In the online store of military clothing «Штурм» you will find a wide range of military clothing and clothing for outdoor activities, as well as a wide variety of paraphernalia. A wide selection of clothes, shoes, uniforms, airsoft shops, cylinders, weapons, masks."</string>
    <string name="id_140">"«Военторг ДиСи» - army store in Kyiv. Military uniform, weapons, equipment and accessories. Clothing for fishing and hunting."</string>
    <string name="id_141">"HobbyTorg.com - online store of goods for hobbies."</string>
    <string name="id_142">"If you need a good hookah or accessories for it, pay attention to the ST-Market store. This site contains the best models of hookahs that delight with their size and design. Here you can choose a practical option for yourself or a luxurious one - for a gift to a friend or colleague."</string>
    <string name="id_143">"The main direction of the store - goods for knitting and felting."</string>
    <string name="id_144">"«Голка» - online store of goods for sewing and needlework. Fabrics, accessories, embroidery, goods for needlework. In the store, each needlewoman will find everything she needs to make an outfit for herself and her loved ones. Everything is here, from inexpensive but beautiful fabrics to exclusive fabrics from Italy."</string>
    <string name="id_145">"Colorsound's online music store features leading manufacturers of musical equipment. Delivery across all Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_146">"Prefabricated models, scale models and radio-controlled models. The Modeli.com.ua online store offers to buy prefabricated models of ships, cars, aircraft, military equipment, etc. at affordable prices. on the site modeli.com.ua. A wide range: plastic and wooden models of all sizes from global manufacturing companies."</string>
    <string name="id_147">"ETNOHATA - online store of Ukrainian products. The store specializes in goods made in the Ukrainian national style. Everything presented in our online store is made in Ukraine by the best masters of their field."</string>
    <string name="id_148">"Online store of computer games "Games Collection" offers a wide range of original products from leading Ukrainian and foreign manufacturers. A wide range of game consoles and accessories. Games for consoles XBOX 360, PSP, PSP Vita, PS3."</string>
    <string name="id_149">"Legendary Ray-Ban sunglasses (RayBan, Raybans, Ray Ben, Ray Ban) are now convenient to buy online in Ukraine: choose several models, try them on during delivery and leave the best ones. Only original rebans from the official distributor."</string>
    <string name="id_150">"«ВАШЕ ЗДОРОВЬЕ» - a network of stores of medical equipment and health products: medical equipment, wheelchairs, medical beds, crutches, walkers, toilet chairs, corsets, bandages, orthopedic insoles and mattresses, blood pressure monitors, glucometers, inhalers, dry closets, water filters and many other products ."</string>
    <string name="id_151">"In the online store you can buy a variety of contact lenses from world manufacturers and care products for them. Wide choice, consultations."</string>
    <string name="id_152">"«Мед-Шоп» - a large assortment of goods for health and for the home. «Мед-Шоп» sells water activators, quartz lamps, magnetotherapy devices, breathing simulators and much more."</string>
    <string name="id_153">"Our online store is one of the leading trading platforms in the ua net for the sale of orthopedic products, medical equipment and rehabilitation products. Our store has the widest range of orthopedic products, such as insoles, ortho shoes, bandages and corsets, compression stockings and much more. We offer our customers the widest range of orthopedic products, rehabilitation and medical equipment, products for hygiene, beauty and health."</string>
    <string name="id_154">"Online store of medical and preventive cosmetics Goldenfarm.com.ua - elite natural cosmetics, health products, dietary supplements, vitamins, weight loss products."</string>
    <string name="id_155">"«Здоровая Лавка» is an online store of environmentally friendly products for safe house cleaning, natural beauty and healthy eating. In the online store you will find: organic food, everything for aromatherapy, environmental detergents and household chemicals, organic cosmetics, eco-friendly products for the home and much more."</string>
    <string name="id_156">"«Био Украина» - organic natural products of the highest quality: organic cosmetics, detergents, food, clothing and goods for children and pregnant women, for the home."</string>
    <string name="id_157">"Apteka911.com.ua – the official online supermarket of the Apteka911 chain: a complete catalog of medicines and health products, indicating the availability in each pharmacy throughout Ukraine. Pharmacy chain 9–1–1 has more than 600 pharmacies. On the Apteka911 website, you can order medicines daily, 24 hours a day. You can pick up the order by self-delivery from a network of pharmacies or order delivery through the companies Nova Poshta, Ukrposhta or courier delivery. Apteka911 means low prices, special promotions and a discount system."</string>
    <string name="id_158">"«АПТЕКА 24» - online ordering medicines throughout Ukraine - low prices, same day delivery, wide range, 24/7 call center. Apteka24.ua - low prices for medicines online. «АПТЕКА 24» is one of the largest pharmacy chains in Ukraine, the pharmacy network is represented in 20 cities of Ukraine. You can receive your order at the pharmacy of our network on the same or the next day, at the partner pharmacy - the next day."</string>
    <string name="id_159">"«Аптека Плюс» - online pharmacy with delivery. «Аптека Плюс» is low prices, quality assurance, authenticity of all medicines, customer confidence. In the online pharmacy aptekaplus.com.ua you can buy medicines with delivery throughout Ukraine. On the «Аптека Плюс» website, ordering medicines online is simple, fast and convenient."</string>
    <string name="id_160">"Tabletki.ua - search and reservation of medicines in pharmacies, thousands of pharmacies throughout Ukraine. Find the right medicine, compare prices in pharmacies and book at a discount. Tabletki.ua - save your time and money when buying medicines. How it works? 1. Find the desired product on the site; 2. Book at a convenient pharmacy at a suitable price; 3. Pick up the ordered goods at a convenient time."</string>
    <string name="id_161">"Add.ua is an online pharmacy of drugs and medicines. Low prices, all in stock, delivery throughout Ukraine. In the add.ua online pharmacy you can purchase: medicines, pharmacy cosmetics, children's products, products for mothers, sunscreens, medical products, hygiene products, vitamins and dietary supplements. Delivery: by courier, New mail, Ukrposhta, pickup from a network of pharmacies."</string>
    <string name="id_162">"Online pharmacy online-apteka.com.ua - online reservation of medications and medicines at an affordable price with delivery to the nearest Med-Service™ pharmacy in Ukraine. Online pharmacy Med-Service offers a wide range of medicines and cosmetics. Online-apteka.com.ua is a fast service that operates 24 hours a day, seven days a week. In the online pharmacy online-apteka.com.ua, you can quickly buy medicines at a low price with delivery to the nearest pharmacy (a network of pharmacies in every city throughout Ukraine)."</string>
    <string name="id_163">"«1 Соціальна Аптека» is a modern online pharmacy that is developing dynamically. Today, the pharmacy offers more than 10 thousand items of medicines, cosmetic products, vitamins, care products and accessories. «1 Соціальна Аптека» is: high quality service; the possibility of booking medicines online; comprehensive information and consulting support; prompt delivery of products."</string>
    <string name="id_164">"Aptekar.ua - online pharmacy «АПТЕКАРЬ» - the best range of medical products, we guarantee authenticity and quality. «АПТЕКАРЬ» network of pharmacies offers a wide range of medicines and medical products. The aptekar.ua online pharmacy catalog contains: medicines, vitamins and dietary supplements, medical cosmetics, medical products, products for mom and baby, beauty and care products, daily hygiene products, health products. The online pharmacy aptekar.ua regularly holds promotions, sales, and discounts. Order online - it will be cheaper!"</string>
    <string name="id_165">"Online store of wipers, wiper blades. Delivery across Kyiv and to regions."</string>
    <string name="id_166">"In the «АвтоБрат» online store you can buy various accessories for cars - a large assortment, reasonable prices, delivery in Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_167">"Auto tuning and accessories. Wholesale and Retail. Tuning SUVs, pickups, jeeps, body kit 4x4. Sale of auto accessories, tuning, body kits, attachments in Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_168">"Automobile, motorcycle accumulator at low prices. Delivery, Discounts, Promotions! Battery supermarket, all brands, Varta (Varta), MEDALIST (medalist), BOSCH (Bosch), ISTA (Ista), A-Mega, etc."</string>
    <string name="id_169">"Online store selling automotive products and auto accessories."</string>
    <string name="id_170">"The Multibox store offers a wide selection of car trunks from leading manufacturers Thule, Mont Blanc, Fapa, Hapro. - car roof racks (car cargo boxes, racks (mounts) for skis and snowboards, for bicycles, boats); - universal trunks (crossbars) for cars with roof rails, gutters, smooth roof; - trunks for transportation of household goods, luggage racks, baskets; - accessories for cargo transportation. Rental, installation of trunks, consultations."</string>
    <string name="id_171">"On the Internet showcase "130" you will find almost everything for your car. Consultants will provide you with comprehensive information and help you find exactly what you are looking for. At "130" you can buy heated seats, a DVR, a head unit, GPS, xenon, an alarm system, a subwoofer, acoustics, parking sensors, an amplifier. Delivery Kyiv, Ukraine"</string>
    <string name="id_172">"Autoshop «Автошара» offers a large selection of auto products and auto accessories. Delivery across Kyiv and Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_173">"Massive.ua is an online spare parts store where you can buy car parts in Ukraine at competitive prices. A very large range of auto parts for different types of car brands, with different methods of delivery and payment."</string>
    <string name="id_174">"Wide range of auto electrics. In the store you can purchase any parts and elements that make up the electrical part of the car."</string>
    <string name="id_175">"Spare parts for Chinese cars are inexpensive. Auto parts for Chery, Geely (Geely), Great Wall (GREAT WALL), BYD, Lifan | asiacentr.com.ua (Asia Center)."</string>
    <string name="id_176">"DOK.ua - online auto parts store - here you can buy spare parts for cars. The DOK online store contains a complete catalog of spare parts. DOK.ua is assistance in the selection and search for auto parts, the best price and delivery in Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_177">"Online auto parts store «АвтоКлад». Auto parts for cars and trucks with delivery in Kyiv, Donetsk, Lvov and Ukraine. «АвтоКлад» company is a leading seller of auto parts in Ukraine, an official partner of KYB, DENSO, ZF, FM in Ukraine. In Avtoklad you can buy inexpensive auto parts for cars and trucks of original quality, oils and chemicals from Castrol, Shell, Mobil, Liqui Molly, Statoil. Good price for spare parts, convenient selection of spare parts from catalogs."</string>
    <string name="id_178">"The VCE online store is a large catalog of auto parts. More than 200,000 items. Payment upon receipt. Discounts up to -15% for regular customers. Spare parts for Korean and European cars."</string>
    <string name="id_179">"Online store of auto parts for foreign cars Exist.ua - electronic spare parts catalog. Auto parts available and under the order. Delivery. EXIST.UA is the largest Ukrainian online store of auto parts and auto products."</string>
    <string name="id_180">"Online auto parts store japan-cars.com.ua. Here you can buy spare parts for Japanese and Korean cars in Kyiv and with delivery in Ukraine. Large selection and electronic spare parts catalog, incl. by VIN."</string>
    <string name="id_182">"Online store "AUTOSHINI" offers a huge range of tires and wheels - summer tires, winter tires, alloy wheels. Delivery of auto tires and wheels throughout Ukraine - Kyiv, Kharkov, Donetsk, Odessa, Dnepropetrovsk, Zaporozhye, Lviv. Autoshini.com - the lowest prices, huge assortment, return, guarantee."</string>
    <string name="id_183">"Online store «Шипшина» - tires, wheels and batteries - buy with delivery in Ukraine. Firm «Шипшина» is a network that combines shops for motorists, wholesale sales centers, tire shops, as well as the service - CAR ASSISTANCE «Шипшина», which operates throughout Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_184">"АвтоСезон.ua - online store of tires and wheels with delivery in Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_185">"Online store Rezina.cc - sale of tires and wheels. Buy summer and winter tires in Kharkov with delivery in Ukraine. Acceptable prices for alloy wheels and car tires (tires) of all brands and sizes. Online store of tires and wheels REZINA.CC - here you can profitably buy high-quality tires and wheels in Ukraine!"</string>
    <string name="id_186">"The «RADIUS» online store offers a wide range of tires and wheels from many manufacturers. Summer tires, winter tires, all season tires. Large selection of discs. Delivery across Kyiv and all Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_187">"Online tire store «Аскания-шина» offers to buy tires and wheels Pirelli, Michelin, Cooper, Yokohama, Roadstone and Rockstone, Good Year, Dunlop, Fulda, Sava, Debica, Continental, Bridgestone, Ceat, Hankook, Nokian, Uniroyal, Semperit, Kumho etc."</string>
    <string name="id_188">"Alfashina.ua - online store of tires and wheels. In the «Альфа Шина» store, you can buy summer and winter tires, car rims, tires and wheels for cars at competitive prices in Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_181">"Do you want to buy tires and wheels for cars without prepayment? Online store infoshina.com.ua. Large selection and free shipping throughout Ukraine! Winter and summer tires from Michelin, Nokian, Bridgestone, Goodyear, Continental, Pirelli, Toyo, Hankook, Dunlop, Cordiant, Yokohama, Sava, Fulda, BF Goodrich, Tigar and many others."</string>
    <string name="id_189">"КлімаТрон is a store of air conditioners and climate equipment. The lowest prices in Kharkiv and Ukraine. Product availability in stock. Credit. Installment Help in choosing an air conditioner. The online store klimatron.ua offers the sale of air conditioners, gas street heaters, heating boilers, flue-ventilation units, thermal curtains, heat pumps."</string>
    <string name="id_190">"Online store - health products, household appliances, climate equipment."</string>
    <string name="id_191">"Internet shop «Кліматика» - boilers, boilers, gas water heaters. Online store "Climatica" is a climate project of the company "Artel" since 1995, the official dealer of brands: JUNKERS (Germany), DAIKIN (Japan). The company offers a wide range of climate and heating equipment that can be purchased with installation and warranty."</string>
    <string name="id_192">"«23 Цельсия» provides services for the selection, installation, warranty and post-warranty maintenance of air conditioners of all brands and manufacturers, we also offer to purchase from us the climatic equipment you are interested in. The list of our interests includes work ONLY with climate equipment. Turning to us, you turn to professionals in their field."</string>
    <string name="id_193">"Internet-shop of climate technology «ТЕПЛОСФЕРА»: sales of opaluval equipment, water heaters, air conditioners and plumbing equipment from leading European manufacturers. A wide range, accept prices. Official guarantee Delivery throughout Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_194">"Climatic equipment - «ЕкоДом»! Ionizers, humidifiers, cleaners, water filters, dehumidifiers, air conditioners, heaters."</string>
    <string name="id_195">"ТЕПЛОТА.COM.UA - online store of climatic equipment for heating. Large selection of equipment for repair and replacement of heating. Boilers, columns, water heaters, radiators, convectors, air conditioners, pumps, water filters, spare parts and equipment installation."</string>
    <string name="id_196">"LORA.UA - online store of tableware. Lora tableware store chain provides a huge selection of tableware. In the store you can buy any dishes for the kitchen, dining room, bar or restaurant. Here you can buy kitchen utensils, tableware, glasses, pans, pots, sets of dishes, knives, teapots, sets, mugs, cups, cutlery, cutting boards, sushi dishes."</string>
    <string name="id_197">"Internet shop of utensils: utensils in Kyiv, a huge selection of utensils."</string>
    <string name="id_198">"Online store of the official representative of the trademarks BergHOFF, Amefa, Roesle and Zwilling in the western region of Ukraine. We offer a full range of products from the most famous brands of tableware for both home and professional use: crockery, accessories, glassware, porcelain, cutlery, knives, manicure sets, children's products…"</string>
    <string name="id_199">"Crockery and accessories for professional kitchen. Promaster is an online tableware store. Choose and buy utensils for professional kitchens in the Promaster utensils online store in Kyiv, Kharkov, Donetsk and Dnepropetrovsk."</string>
    <string name="id_200">"The online store of dishes BergHOFF.dp.ua in Dnepropetrovsk offers kitchenware Berghoff, Risoli, Frabosk. Large assortment of various kitchen utensils."</string>
    <string name="id_201">"Krauff - German elite tableware. Krauff.com is the official online store for Krauff tableware. Free shipping. Quality assurance. The store presents the most complete catalog of Krauff dishes: crockery sets, frying pans and stewpans, cutlery, plates and bowls, kitchen tools, pots and ladles, tea and coffee utensils, thermoses and thermo mugs, knives and knife sets, trays, bread bins, graters and cutting boards, spice sets and various kitchen accessories."</string>
    <string name="id_202">"Crockery Luminarc (Lyuminark) in the online store Luminarc.in.ua. Online store of high quality, practical and very beautiful tableware from France - Luminarc. Luminarc.in.ua is the official distributor of the ARC International plant in Ukraine, the Le Mage company."</string>
    <string name="id_203">"Online store of dishes posuda.ua - the official representation of BergHOFF, Roesle, Amefa, Blomus, Continenta, Revol, Bredemeijer, Cook&amp;Co."</string>
    <string name="id_204">"The online store offers a wide range of quality leather haberdashery at reasonable prices. Bags, clutches, briefcases, travel bags, wallets and wallets, accessories, belts."</string>
    <string name="id_205">"Online store E-torba - bags and accessories, wallets, wallets, belts, purses, briefcases, jewelry boxes."</string>
    <string name="id_206">"In the online store Bagboom.com.ua you can buy leather bags for men and women, briefcases, wallets, purses, belts, suitcases, backpacks, umbrellas, clutches and cosmetic bags. Delivery across Kyiv and Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_207">"Shop and wholesale warehouse of bags and accessories, elite leather goods - wholesale and retail, courier delivery. Women's leather bags, leatherette, pressed leather, briefcases, purses, wallets, wallets, belts, scarves, shawls, sunglasses."</string>
    <string name="id_208">"Official online store Neri Karra in Ukraine. Free shipping across Ukraine. NERI-KARRA.COM.UA is the official representative of Neri Karra in Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_209">"The LeGRAND online bag store offers women's bags, fashion branded bags, leather bags, men's bags, genuine leather products and luxury leather goods."</string>
    <string name="id_210">"Travel Store - online store of fashionable bags, travel luggage and travel accessories. In the store you can buy: suitcases, travel bags, bags on wheels and much more from world famous brands such as BRIC'S, Delsey, Samsonite, V&amp;V, Vito Torelli, Franco Cesare, NOBEL, VOLUM, EPOL, Slavnik, Tergan. Always new collections. Delivery across all Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_211">"Online store of goods for animals Zooparadise offers you a huge range of goods for animals. Food and accessories for pets in Kharkiv."</string>
    <string name="id_212">"A pet store (online store) of pet products ezoo.com.ua offers to buy pet supplies with delivery in Ukraine - Kyiv, Kharkov, Donetsk, Odessa"</string>
    <string name="id_213">"«Зоокомплекс» - an online store of pet supplies in Ukraine - aquariums, lamps, products for dogs and cats, food, pet supplies and everything for animals."</string>
    <string name="id_214">"The online store of goods for animals «Рыжий Кот» offers food, pet products, goods for animals, veterinary drugs."</string>
    <string name="id_215">"Online Pet Shop «Зверушка» offers a wide range of high-quality pet food and products from the best brands and brands. Here you can buy food for dogs and cats, birds and parrots, chinchillas, rabbits and hamsters … as well as all the necessary products for the successful maintenance of your pets: cages and aviaries, scratching posts and feeders, soft places, houses, sun loungers and much more."</string>
    <string name="id_216">"«Ветмаркет» - online store of veterinary medicines and pet products. Catalog of veterinary goods - preparations for animals. Constant availability of the necessary inventory, wholesale prices, high quality. Delivery across all Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_217">"PET STORE ZOO.com.ua offers a wide range of pet supplies from global manufacturers - pet supplies for dogs, cats, birds, rodents, fish, reptiles and horses. All pet supplies can be purchased both online and by visiting a retail pet store in Kyiv."</string>
    <string name="id_218">"Pet supplies, pet products - in the ZooFavorit online pet store you can choose all the necessary pet products for your pets: food, vitamins, products for rest and development of the animal, preparations and accessories for caring for a dog, cat, birds, etc."</string>
    <string name="id_219">"In the online store "DuDa" you can buy bongs, pipes and hookahs. Wide selection and best prices. Fast delivery across Kyiv and Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_220">"Purchase and delivery of goods from the USA, from the eBay auction and other US online stores to Ukraine and other countries. Ease of search, ease of ordering, delivery guarantee."</string>
    <string name="id_221">"Video surveillance systems, video surveillance, video surveillance equipment, home video surveillance. The WorldMotion online store offers equipment for security systems (video surveillance, burglar alarms, access control) of high quality and at an affordable price. Each client will be able to get professional advice in the store."</string>
    <string name="id_222">"«Фотобум» online store offers: advertising materials, cutting plotters, thermal presses, photo paper, self-adhesive labels, printer cartridges. Equipment and materials for the production of advertising souvenirs wholesale and retail."</string>
    <string name="id_223">"«Altshop» Alternative Energy Center: solar collectors, solar batteries, wind turbines, heat pumps, solid fuel boilers."</string>
    <string name="id_224">"«Абразив» online store presents a wide range of tools for individual protection, power tools, petrol tools, and hand tools. Direct deliveries."</string>
    <string name="id_225">"In the online store "Dumok.com.ua" you can buy a hookah of the highest quality. Here are the best hookahs made according to traditional technologies in eastern countries - Egypt, Syria and Lebanon."</string>
    <string name="id_226">"«ЧП Ворон» - online store: electronic components (radio components, microcircuits, transistors, resistors, capacitors, thyristors, connectors, relays, diodes, stabilizers, electrical tools, soldering equipment, etc.). Supply of equipment to all regions. Direct contracts with manufacturers, reasonable prices, professional technical support."</string>
    <string name="id_227">"Online store of tiles and plumbing Keramis - everything for bathroom renovation, best prices and delivery of the order is always on time. In the online store keramis.com.ua you can buy products of world famous brandsGrohe, Hansgrohe, Paradyz, Cerrad, Ravak, Radaway, Kolo, Roca, Pool Spa, Opozcno, Pamesa, Rako, Atlas Concorde, Ceramika Gres, Laris, Bosch, Elstead , Marburg, Balterio, Barlinek, Rehau and many others."</string>
    <string name="id_228">"Online store «Кулибин» - professional tools, garden equipment, welding equipment with delivery in Vinnitsa and throughout Ukraine. The catalog of the online store kulibin.com.ua includes: garden products, welding equipment, power tools, pneumatic tools, hand tools, auto service tools, measuring tools, protective equipment, special equipment, irrigation equipment, cleaning equipment."</string>
    <string name="id_229">"Online store with a large selection of wallpapers. We have universal wallpaper, paintable wallpaper, nursery and kitchen wallpaper, as well as photo wallpapers. We work with well-known proven manufacturers: Rasch (Rush), Marburg (Marburg), Erismann (Erismann) and others. We can also offer laminate and parquet boards from Tarkett, Balterio, Classen, Berry Alloc, Kaindl, Boen. We regularly hold promotions, there is a system of discounts. And consultants will help you get answers to all your questions."</string>
    <string name="id_230">"Internet hypermarket «СтройМаг» is one of the largest building materials stores in Ukraine. Here you can buy high-quality goods for home renovation or gardening. We offer high quality products and work exclusively with trusted manufacturers."</string>
    <string name="id_231">"«Транс Стоун» LLC is the only highly specialized company in Ukraine supplying artificial stone. The company is engaged in the production and sale of artificial stone products."</string>
    <string name="id_232">"The online store of paintings «Шедевр» is the largest online gallery in Ukraine and the CIS where you can buy paintings by contemporary artists. We have a wide range of modern paintings, antique paintings, Ukrainian artists, icons, custom-made paintings, reproductions of paintings by famous masters, and much more."</string>
    <string name="id_233">"Online store ALLO - hardware and electronics store in Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_234">"The online stationery store «Юканц» offers stationery for the office with delivery. The company «Юканц» offers all the stationery necessary for work of high quality and at competitive prices with prompt delivery directly to your office."</string>
    <string name="id_235">"«СНПЧ INKSYSTEM» for color printing. The Originalam.net online store offers to buy CISS for Epson, Canon, HP and Brother printers, refillable cartridges and photo paper. Sale of printers, MFPs, plotters with an installed ink supply system. Repair of printing devices of any firms."</string>
    <string name="id_236">"The online store provides the widest selection of office supplies at attractive prices. Stationery, presentation equipment, office equipment and equipment, post-press equipment, banking equipment, safes, metal furniture."</string>
    <string name="id_237">"Online store papirus.com.ua - everything you need for the office - 10,000 items of the main assortment and goods on order. Only high-quality stationery for any budget. Stationery for every taste."</string>
    <string name="id_238">"Online stationery store at a bargain price. The ability to buy stationery online, or place an order by phone."</string>
    <string name="id_239">"The Aragon.com.ua online store provides customers with a wide selection of office supplies: office and home stationery, paper products, office equipment and much more."</string>
    <string name="id_240">"«Камертон» - online store of stationery and children's toys, Kharkiv. 3000 items. Delivery across Ukraine. Bulk prices. Comprehensive office services. Office equipment. Household goods. Printing Services. Kids toys. Computer parts."</string>
    <string name="id_241">"«Палей» - online store has a large selection of stationery and accessories - office supplies necessary for the daily optimal operation of the business. Paper, diaries and notepads, accounting forms, pens and rods, calculators and phones, folders and briefcases, pencils, felt-tip pens, markers, rubber bands and sharpeners, glue, corrector, paints and brushes, office equipment and supplies, disks and flash drives, desktop accessories and adhesive tape and a number of other goods delivered directly to the office."</string>
    <string name="id_242">"«КанцКапитал» - stationery for office and school, stationery wholesale and retail. Here you can buy stationery with delivery in Kyiv and Ukraine. A wide selection and affordable prices for stationery."</string>
    <string name="id_243">"Online store «Акцент-Сервис» presents a wide range of stationery, from the best manufacturers of stationery. Stationery for the office, for home, as well as everything you need for the child to school."</string>
    <string name="id_244">"We present to your attention the exclusive collections of the French underwear of the Fashion House Florange. Our collections are unique! They are created by French designers only for the Florange trademark and are produced in limited quantities."</string>
    <string name="id_245">"The Astratex.ua online store offers: women's underwear, erotic lingerie, luxurious shirts, elegant tights."</string>
    <string name="id_246">"Internet shop of underwear and clothes. When buying from 3 different items, a 23% discount is charged."</string>
    <string name="id_247">"The online store offers lingerie, erotic and lingerie in large sizes and for slim girls."</string>
    <string name="id_248">"Mari-m.com.ua - online store for lingerie from the best manufacturers Milavitsa, Kleo, Lauma, Key, V.O.V.A, Legs and others. Delivery across all Ukraine. If it doesn't fit, we'll exchange it!"</string>
    <string name="id_249">"Atlantic underwear online store in Ukraine offers to buy underwear in Kyiv. Large selection of beautiful seamless underwear. Delivery of goods across all Ukraine is carried out."</string>
    <string name="id_250">"Online lingerie store «069» offers to buy lingerie, erotic lingerie, lingerie wholesale."</string>
    <string name="id_251">"Online store of lingerie «Алиса» offers lingerie from European manufacturers, large sizes of lingerie. Delivery across all Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_252">"Online lingerie store "Darin" offers to buy lingerie, men's underwear, erotic lingerie."</string>
    <string name="id_253">"The Lanett underwear online store presents a wonderful selection of women's, men's and children's underwear."</string>
    <string name="id_254">"National online store of books, stationery, toys and school supplies."</string>
    <string name="id_255">"«Лавка Бабуин» is an online bookstore. Online store «Лавка Бабуин» - thousands of goods of various genres and themes that you can order at the best prices. Large selection, good prices."</string>
    <string name="id_256">"Yakaboo is the leading online store in Ukraine, a leader in the field of book sales."</string>
    <string name="id_257">"The online bookstore «Буклетка» offers to buy textbooks, dictionaries, dictionaries, grammar, manuals, educational and methodical literature for secondary and high schools with delivery in Ukraine, wholesale and retail. Here you can order and buy reference books, notebooks for schools, worksheets, copybooks, atlases and contour maps, collections of problems, manuals with delivery across Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_258">"Schooldream.com.ua - online bookstore «Шкільна література». In the schooldream.com.ua online store, you can buy textbooks, manuals, notebooks from various subjects. School and preschool literature is presented here."</string>
    <string name="id_259">"Book Club «Клуб Семейного Досуга» - book novelties, the best books, gift and exclusive editions through the distribution of catalogs."</string>
    <string name="id_260">"Bookstore «Букля» offers books for every taste. A wide selection of literature for any reader. Booklya.ua - online bookstore with delivery throughout Ukraine. «Букля» offers about 210 thousand titles of books of various genres, topics and formats."</string>
    <string name="id_261">"Book24.ua is an online book store with over 30,000 titles of books of various genres. Book24 is an online bookstore that makes it easy to find and purchase quality products. Here you can find books for all occasions: works of world classics, best-selling books, educational literature, books for personal growth and business development, books for children, gift books, etc."</string>
    <string name="id_262">"In the online store Kniga.biz.ua you can buy books about business with delivery in Kyiv and Ukraine. It presents a wide range of business literature on the topic: entrepreneurship, management, marketing, sales, finance and economics, communications and negotiations, time management and business planning. The online store kniga.biz.ua always presents the most popular and relevant business books and books for personal development."</string>
    <string name="id_263">"«Книголенд» is an online store of books, gifts and children's goods. In the online bookstore knigoland.com.ua you can buy books and gifts at the best prices in Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_264">"We will help every modern woman in her desire to be beautiful and unique. Our products will add the last detail to your perfect look. Buying from us you get quality at low prices."</string>
    <string name="id_265">"The BestShopping.com.ua online store offers a large selection and an official guarantee for all products. Delivery all over Ukraine Bestshopping.com.ua"</string>
    <string name="id_266">"The network of online stores Miroshop - household appliances, computer equipment, mobile phones, photo and video equipment, electrical lighting, dishes, goods for recreation and tourism, sports goods, household supplies, children's goods, watches, gifts and souvenirs, power tools, garden equipment, medical goods, furniture."</string>
    <string name="id_267">"In the «АКС» online electronics store you can buy mobile phones and accessories, e-books, memory cards, usb-flash drives, mp3 players, digital cameras and other goods at the most fair prices."</string>
    <string name="id_268">"Lvivmarket.com is an online store of goods for every home."</string>
    <string name="id_269">"The best online store in Kyiv - GRENKA.ua. A huge range of books of various genres, games for any console and PC, camping equipment and fishing tackle."</string>
    <string name="id_270">"Online store "PRO100 MARKET" offers a wide range of products: household appliances, audio equipment, auto products, home and garden products, children's products, leisure products."</string>
    <string name="id_271">"Kasta is the most fashionable clothing, footwear and accessories marketplace in Ukraine. Since 2010, Kasta has been opening the best international brands and brands of talented Ukrainian designers to Ukrainians and proving by its own example that buying goods on the Internet is simple, fast and cheap. We are constantly working to ensure that Kasta is the single entry point for all entrepreneurs who want to sell online and is convenient and secure for all online shopping customers."</string>
    <string name="id_272">"«F.ua» is household appliances, garden and repair tools, sports, tourism, books, cosmetics, toys, watches, dishes, laptops, pet products, phones. Everything you buy in our store are certified products that have a manufacturer's warranty. You will not be pushed what you do not need. We not only deliver goods, but also provide service and maintenance. You will never be left without answers to your questions."</string>
    <string name="id_273">"Shop of goods from Italy. The LOWEST prices for wines and products. Here you can buy wine for every taste! A wide range of vintage wines from well-known producers."</string>
    <string name="id_274">"Bel Gusto is an online store that offers to buy food products online: spirits, gastronomy, groceries, confectionery, soft drinks, coffee, tea."</string>
    <string name="id_275">"In the online store you can buy Lavazza coffee beans, ground coffee, coffee capsules, coffee pods, monodose tablets. Italian coffee. Coffee Gemini, Kimbo, Goriziana Caffe, Paulig, Movenpick, Blaser, Dallmayr, Alvaro. Delivery of coffee to the office. Rental of coffee makers for the office. Repair of coffee makers Saeco, Spidem."</string>
    <string name="id_276">"ArtDrink - online store of alcoholic beverages (chacha, tequila, rum, gin, cognac, wine, bitters, whiskey, etc.). Only certified products. We work directly with importers and manufacturers. Has its own import. Delivery across Kyiv and Ukraine. Any payment method."</string>
    <string name="id_277">"«Суши Повар» - a store that represents everything for sushi: ingredients, dishes, accessories for making sushi. In the store you will find many healthy recipes for making sushi."</string>
    <string name="id_278">"Zakaz.ua grocery delivery service is the official partner of the «Ашан» supermarket chain in providing services for ordering, assembling and delivering food and household goods. You can place an order for the assembly and delivery of products to your home right now - online ordering in supermarkets through the site is available around the clock. Our call center is open from 9:00 to 22:00 and will be happy to help you place a new order and answer any questions about orders already placed. Delivery of products takes place from 11:00 to 22:00."</string>
    <string name="id_279">"«Чайний Дворик» - online store of tea and coffee. Here you can buy tea, coffee and accessories. We consider it our main goal to find and subsequently sell the best quality and price weight tea, always fresh coffee beans, exquisite and various accessories and utensils. Home and office delivery available. «Чайний Дворик» - the benefits of taste in every cup."</string>
    <string name="id_280">"Products from Italy and other European countries. The main activity of our company is the delivery of high-quality food products of European quality to restaurants and pizzerias in Kiev, as well as other cities of Ukraine. The company was created to meet the needs of catering establishments in high-quality food products from European countries."</string>
    <string name="id_281">"Our store is a place where you can buy not only caviar, but also seafood with delivery throughout Ukraine. This is ensured by direct cooperation with time-proven suppliers and producers: Caviar House Lemberg / Lemberg, Zarendom / Zarendom, Kaspia Caviar / Caspia Caviar, thanks to which the quality of our products is always at the highest level. You can buy the following products from us: Caviar products of various types (red, black, pike, cod, etc.); Various seafood (fish, crabs, etc.); Several types of high-quality coffee (ground and grain); Fish roe is our main product and we strictly monitor its quality, checking each jar before sending it to the customer. We also guarantee a quick response to every application made on our website."</string>
    <string name="id_282">"The products of the «Волинські солодощі» trade mark participated in many prestigious regional, national and international confectionery exhibitions and competitions. Our products meet all the requirements of ДСТУ, have quality certificates and comply with sanitary and hygienic standards. Sweets do not contain preservatives, stabilizers and GMOs. Raw materials undergo careful selection and quality control in laboratories."</string>
    <string name="id_283">"«КофейОК», coffeeok.com.ua - an online store selling coffee, coffee machines and various coffee accessories from the world's leading manufacturers BlaserCafe, Cafe Badilatti, Lavazza, Kimbo, Lucaffe, Julius Meinl, Starbucks, Movenpik, Dallmayr, Illy, Musetti."</string>
    <string name="id_284">"Online store of Chinese tea Chinachay.com.ua offers a wide selection of teas of the most famous Chinese varieties. The assortment includes a choice of such varieties as: "puer", "da hong pao" and "te guan yin". All teas are offered exclusively from producers. As well as crockery and accessories. Delivery to any city of Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_285">"In the online store you can order the best varieties of tea and coffee. Only the best grades of tea of the «Світ чаю» brand and coffee of the «Віденська кава» brand are presented."</string>
    <string name="id_286">"Online tea shop from all over the world! Here you will find tea for every taste, as well as original dishes and accessories for the tea ceremony."</string>
    <string name="id_287">"The Ukrainian coffee company delivers the best varieties of natural coffee (green, roasted, ground and flavored coffee) throughout Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_288">""Grusha.ua" is a national online store that specializes in freshly roasted coffee and whose catalog contains proven brands of a noble instant and brewed drink from different regions of Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_289">"Online shop and tea room in Kyiv. Created by a student of the Japanese tea school Uraenke. Tea ceremonies, events, tea school, sale of tea and utensils."</string>
    <string name="id_290">"«АВТ-Маркет» - online store of coffee, tea, coffee machines and accessories. We produce: single grade Arabica, beans, grain, plantation coffee. Delivery of coffee in Kyiv, Ukraine from 1000 UAH for free."</string>
    <string name="id_291">"Online store of plants: indoor fruit plants: pineapples, bananas, indoor lemons, oranges, tangerines, other exotic plants. Wide selection of orchids. You can also buy soil, fertilizers, pots for plants."</string>
    <string name="id_292">"Entrust the delivery of your bouquet to professionals. Delivery service to more than 200 countries of the world, 10 flower shops in Ukraine, showroom in Kyiv, representative offices in major cities of the СНД."</string>
    <string name="id_293">"We will congratulate your loved ones, relatives, business partners on your behalf on the day you have appointed anywhere in Ukraine and the world. Flowers, gifts."</string>
    <string name="id_294">"Flower shop BuketLand delivers flowers and gifts in Ukraine. Buketland.com.ua is an urgent delivery of flowers to Kyiv 24/7 - only fresh flowers at competitive prices with free delivery in Kyiv. BuketLand is one of the best flower delivery services in the Ukrainian market."</string>
    <string name="id_295">"Flowers.ua is a national flower and gift delivery service in Ukraine and the world. We have been delivering flowers and gifts for over 17 years and have vast experience in organizing congratulations at a high level! We also understand that our work is not only the delivery of flowers, but, first of all, the delivery of a good mood, the transfer of your emotions to dear people at a distance!"</string>
    <string name="id_296">"We produce and import seeds, bulbs, flower clubs. (Products from Ukraine and Holland). Our prices will pleasantly surprise you, because we do not chase excess profits, but work for the future, understanding all the realities of the market. We provide a 100% guarantee of quality and compliance for all products, which excludes any worries on your part."</string>
    <string name="id_297">"Agro-Market.ua has more than 15,000 products on its website and all of them are available in the company's personal warehouse, and orders are sent to customers directly from the store and without intermediaries. This helps to avoid situations with product substitution or slow delivery of orders."</string>
    <string name="id_298">"«КвітоСвіт» online store delivers goods only in Ukraine. The store sells flowering perennials, indoor plants, fruit and berry seedlings, garden tools."</string>
    <string name="id_299">"We grow seedlings, seedlings and cuttings of annual and perennial plants in pots and cassettes, ready for planting in open ground, large pots, containers, etc. All plants are sent throughout Ukraine. The packaging is high quality and professional. On the Ukrainian market since 2010. We use seeds and cuttings only from world famous companies."</string>
    <string name="id_300">"BIjouella - wholesale jewelry from China at wholesale prices."</string>
    <string name="id_301">"Shamballa Exclusive: Shamballa bracelets made of natural stones."</string>
    <string name="id_302">"The French brand of jewelry Les Nereides (Le Nereid) is known all over the world. The authors of the brand are designers Enzo and Pascal Amadeo. The name Les Nereides means "sea nymphs". Today, Les Nereides jewelry can be bought in a network of boutiques located in France, Great Britain, Belgium, USA, Australia, Italy, Indonesia, Taiwan, China, Japan, Hong Kong."</string>
    <string name="id_303">"SUNSTONES.com.ua - jewelry made of natural stones, bijouterie. Jewelry made of natural stone wholesale and retail. Stone gifts wholesale and retail. Bijouterie from original gems large and small wholesale. Direct deliveries from China and Turkey."</string>
    <string name="id_304">"Zakolochka wholesale jewelry online store - sale of inexpensive and stylish jewelry. Minimum order amount: UAH 300."</string>
    <string name="id_305">"Shop of beads and accessories «Конфитюр». Buy beads. Courses and master classes Needlework, a wide range of beads and accessories for jewelry. Master - classes, lessons on making jewelry. Homemade products. Wire ornaments."</string>
    <string name="id_306">"If you adore jewelry and cannot imagine your image without these accessories, if you want to make a fashionable gift - welcome to the online jewelry store «Бьютик»."</string>
    <string name="id_307">"Xstyle is an online store of beautiful clothes and shoes. Fashionable branded clothing at affordable prices. Fast delivery to Kyiv, Kharkov, Dnipro and other cities."</string>
    <string name="id_308">"Browse our jewelry catalog now to find the perfect finishing touches to your look tomorrow. We appreciate your choice. Beauty is work and a little luck. Always yours, ZIGZAG.com.ua!"</string>
    <string name="id_309">"Online store of jewelry and jewelry with stones «ФРОМСТОНЕС». A large assortment, excellent quality, good prices and fast delivery."</string>
    <string name="id_310">"SolPower is the official importer and dealer of solar chargers, external batteries (Power bank), battery cases and other devices that increase the operating time of mobile equipment and their direct recharging. Narrow specialization allows us to provide the widest possible choice of portable chargers. We supply devices exclusively from well-known world brands, manufactured in the USA, China, Europe, which allows us to completely eliminate manufacturing defects and provide a quality guarantee."</string>
    <string name="id_311">"The online store «Сетевуха» presents a wide selection of passive, active and server equipment, as well as equipment for video surveillance and telephony systems."</string>
    <string name="id_312">"Online store FotoPapir.com.ua specializes in the sale of consumables for inkjet and laser printing. The online store has both original and compatible cartridges. Large range of photo paper for all types of printing."</string>
    <string name="id_313">"Bezpeka-Shop.com is a security hypermarket and the largest online store for integrated security systems. «Безпека-Шоп» cooperates only with well-known brands and is engaged in the sale, installation and maintenance of equipment."</string>
    <string name="id_314">"Up2date is an online store of electronics and digital equipment. The site presents many categories of goods, where you can choose from accessories for the iPad, iPhone, as well as e-books, watches, headphones, audio and photo equipment, and much more. Also in the online store up2date.com.ua there is a large section on game consoles (game consoles and consoles), which avid gamers will appreciate."</string>
    <string name="id_315">"Topsmart.com.ua - news from the world of technology. Sale of Android media players, action cameras, smartphones and other portable electronics. In the Topsmart.com.ua online store you can buy smart set-top boxes, air guns, action cameras, game joysticks, vacuum cleaner robots and other popular electronics."</string>
    <string name="id_316">"iStore - The official online store for Apple technology in Kyiv and Ukraine. Sale of Apple technology online and in iStor branded stores! iStore.ua is an online store of iStore, a Ukrainian network of stores for Apple technology and related products. Here you can buy equipment - iMac, MacBook Pro, iPad or iPhone as well as accessories for them."</string>
    <string name="id_317">"Online store Citrus: mobile phones, laptops, smartphones, flash drives - Kyiv, Odessa, Ukraine. In our online store you can buy laptops, mobile phones (smartphones) at the lowest prices in Ukraine!"</string>
    <string name="id_318">"Toiler - online store for Apple technology, gadgets and accessories. Toiler online store is a Ukrainian online store specializing in Apple technology and the latest in modern electronic gadgets for life. Here is a full range of original Apple technology. All new Apple products in Ukraine can be bought here!"</string>
    <string name="id_319">"Easybay online store - smartphones, gadgets, accessories. Easybay is an online store of popular gadgets and accessories. Smartphones at the best prices. Large selection of smart appliances. Pickup in Kyiv. Delivery by New Mail across all Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_320">"Online store "JM" - bathroom accessories, chandeliers, lamps, sconces, floor lamps."</string>
    <string name="id_321">"The company «Супермаркет Фитингов» is engaged in the sale of goods for heating and water supply. By contacting us you will receive: professional information, quality products, discounts depending on the volume of the order. Separate offers for construction and assembly organizations."</string>
    <string name="id_322">"Online decor store in Ukraine «Декоратор» is the only one offering unique items for interior design. Our online decor store can proudly announce that more than twenty brands from Italy are collected on the pages of the catalog. Each manufacturer has its own characteristics and brand differences that make its products special. Thanks to such a large assortment offered by the Decor Shop online store, you have a unique opportunity to purchase stylish items for home decoration."</string>
    <string name="id_323">"JYSK is an international retail chain where you can buy home goods. The JYSK company belongs to the Lars Larsen Group. The founder, Lars Larsen, is known in Denmark as the country's leading retailer who always has a "great deal"."</string>
    <string name="id_324">"Our store «Ярмарок декору» offers you a huge range of products, among which you will find both interior items for residential and non-residential premises - vases, paintings, flower pots, candlesticks, lanterns, cages, lamps, photo frames, clocks, as well as thematic and seasonal goods - items for decorating the Easter table, New Year's and Christmas themes, the theme of March 8, St. Valentine's Day, as well as personal items - pins, rims, bandanas."</string>
    <string name="id_325">"Online store «Зернятно» - buy seeds of vegetables, flowers, spices, fodder and green manure salads, as well as mushroom mycelium only from the best suppliers with fast delivery in Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_326">"«МЕБЛИУМ» - online furniture store with smart prices. Children's furniture and office furniture. Buy furniture in Kyiv inexpensively. Home furniture for every taste. Sale of furniture to order and from a warehouse."</string>
    <string name="id_327">"The widest range of chairs, armchairs, tables, furniture for home and office. «КупиСтул» is expert advice, low prices, regular promotions and discounts, delivery in Ukraine. KupiStul.ua - more than 2000 chairs and armchairs - for every taste! Popular categories in the kupistul.ua online store: kitchen chairs, bar stools, office chairs, folding chairs, hanging chairs, child seats, visitor chairs, designer chairs."</string>
    <string name="id_328">"Furniture of the best factories - only high-quality furniture in Kiev and Ukraine, furniture and interior items such as home and office furniture, furniture for the living room, bedroom, nursery, kitchen, study, hallway, tables and chairs, upholstered furniture, furniture walls, all this You will find in the online furniture store «Шуруп»."</string>
    <string name="id_329">"BUY and SLEEP is an online bed linen store where you can buy bed linen from the world's best manufacturers and pay for your purchase directly on the site, it is very convenient and fast. The online store has its own bed linen warehouse. Free shipping across Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_330">"Orthopedic, anatomical mattresses «ТЕП» and home textiles from the manufacturer. The online store «Азбука сна» works without intermediaries and is a representative of the manufacturing company ООО ПКФ «Балакком». Implementation of «ТЕП» mattresses and home textiles throughout Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_331">"Online clothing store in Odessa «Глазурь» - branded clothing at the best prices. In the online store of branded clothing glazur.in.ua you can buy the best fashionable clothes at low prices."</string>
    <string name="id_332">"Online store of sportswear and equipment for martial arts MMA Style. Our MMA store offers you to buy T-shirts, rashguards, shorts and other MMA clothing. The best sportswear and MMA equipment from the brands TapOut, Venum, Bad Boy, Hayabusa, Everlast, Affliction, Shock Doctor, Fairtex, Free-Fight is now available in Ukraine!"</string>
    <string name="id_333">"«МИР ОБУВИ» - current novelties from well-known brands. It is difficult to imagine the elements of a modern person's wardrobe that would be chosen more carefully and thoroughly than shoes. This is more than a stylish accessory: boots, boots, shoes and other models perform a very important function - they are responsible for comfort, and sometimes for the health of the feet."</string>
    <string name="id_334">"In the «Симпатяшка» online store you can buy baby clothes for newborns, clothes for boys, clothes for girls, soft toys, large soft toys, children's toys, porcelain dolls, interior toys, souvenirs, gifts, bedding for children and adults at affordable prices. Delivery across Kyiv and Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_335">"TM «Шалунишка» offers for sale children's shoes made in Ukraine. Our online store specializes in the retail sale of children's shoes for everyday wear, as well as preventive shoes with special orthopedic properties. More than 3000 models, permanent discounts! All products are 100% certified and meet quality requirements. Delivery throughout Ukraine!"</string>
    <string name="id_336">"In our online store BabyStores.com.ua only branded children's clothing and shoes from world brands, including from the USA, are presented. More than 6000 items, 100% original products with a guarantee. Delivery across all Ukraine. Payment upon receipt, after checking and trying on! Cumulative discounts for regular customers. Promotions and sales."</string>
    <string name="id_337">"Online toy store in Dnepropetrovsk MIRAMIDA.com.ua offers children's goods, children's toys - a huge selection, reasonable prices, delivery throughout Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_338">"Internet shop «ТЯГА» - radio-controlled cars, planes, tanks, boats, yachts and radio-controlled helicopters. Delivery - Kyiv, Kharkov, Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_339">"Official online store SWATCH in Ukraine. Online store of watches and jewelry SWATCH. Buy swiss watches SWATCH with delivery in Kyiv."</string>
    <string name="id_340">"Online store of watches Timebar. Official supplier of such brands as Guess, Just Cavalli, Morgan, Mazeratti, Galliano, FCUK, 33 ELEMENT, Nesterov and many others. Shops in Kyiv, Kharkov, Nikolaev and Dnepropetrovsk. Free shipping to any city in Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_341">"Online watch store «Секунда». «Секунда» watch chain stores throughout Ukraine. Quality assurance."</string>
    <string name="id_342">"In the online store «На пределе» you can buy sports goods for various sports. Delivery of sporting goods throughout Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_343">"Online store of useful gifts Podveski.com.ua with delivery in Kyiv, Ukraine. Choose a gift for a birthday, a wedding, an anniversary gift, an anniversary, a business gift, a gift for a woman or a man, a housewarming gift."</string>
    <string name="id_344">"FunFan is a team of professionals who have been delighting their customers with quality products and excellent service for over 20 years. The slogan of our company sounds like this: "Created for the Holiday". That is why we work to help you create an unforgettable holiday according to your wishes."</string>
    <string name="id_345">"Our online store offers a wide range of products that will be of interest to both regular customers and wholesale customers. These include: various latex and foil balls; festive paper paraphernalia of our own production (caps, medals, horns, boxes for sweets, etc.); disposable products for children's celebrations (plates, cups, tablecloths); bright photo zones, posters, foil curtains, photo props for an unforgettable photo session; firecrackers, confetti, smoke balloons; and many other products for Theme Parties."</string>
    <string name="id_346">"All products presented in the catalog can be purchased in retail and wholesale. At the same time, depending on the volume, additional discounts are provided. The online store cooperates with such manufacturers as Gemar (Italy), SHOW (Ukraine), Multitex (China), Flexmetal (Spain). Certified products are characterized by excellent quality, which guarantees exclusively positive emotions from using them."</string>
    <string name="id_347">"For more than 12 years, we have been engaged in the sale of goods for children's parties, adult themed parties, carnival products and paraphernalia. Extensive work experience helps us to choose the most popular and high-quality holiday accessories and paraphernalia in this field."</string>
    <string name="id_348">"All the paraphernalia that you will find on the pages of our online store differs in quality and safety. Thanks to her, sincere smiles and unforgettable photos will be countless at your holiday. And this is the best result of our coordinated work! This love has led us to create an entire empire in the production and wholesale of holiday products. And for more than 5 years now, we have been pleasing Ukrainians with bright and original paraphernalia that helps make any event even brighter and more effective."</string>
    <string name="id_349">"Oniks.ua - online jewelry store. Onyx jewelry company has been successfully operating in the jewelry market of Ukraine for more than 25 years! In the online store oniks.ua you can buy new collections of jewelry at competitive prices. Free delivery of jewelry in Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_350">"Pandora is a world-famous and beloved jewelry brand of Danish origin. The brand that inspires millions of people in the world to new achievements and victories, teaches to love and appreciate its uniqueness. Pandora creates unparalleled jewelry that becomes not just stylish accessories, but carries sensual women's stories, preserves them as an inexhaustible source of inspiration."</string>
    <string name="id_351">"Exrtrem Style online sporting goods store offers a wide range of sporting goods and accessories for all sports. Skis, snowboards, skates, bicycles, tents, backpacks, skateboards."</string>
    <string name="id_352">"Here you can order hiking and climbing equipment, clothes, shoes, everything you need for a pleasant stay and adventure. We are open 24 hours a day, 7 days a week."</string>
    <string name="id_353">"«Крутиголов» store offers metal puzzles, wooden puzzles, plastic puzzles, Rubik's Cube, 3D puzzles, and you can also buy playing cards, board games and magic props from us."</string>
    <string name="id_354">"OpticalMarket offers to choose and buy a microscope, telescope, binoculars, scope. Wide range of products. Delivery to all cities of Ukraine. Discounts for regular customers. Brands of optical and weather devices presented in the online store: Celestron, Sky-Watcher, Kson Optics, Meade, Konus, Hawke Optics, Alpen Optics, Kowa, Vortex, La Crosse, Atomic, Ea2, Oregon Scientific, Explore Scientific, Micros, Ulab, Ningbo, Bresser, Paralux and many more."</string>
    <string name="id_355">"Shop of contact lenses, solutions and accessories with delivery in Kyiv and Ukraine. In the online store you can buy lenses of such world brands as Bausch&amp;Lomb, Ciba Vision, Johnson&amp;Johnson, Cooper Vision, Avizor, Maxima, Sauflon, Zeiss, OKVision, Adore, Alcon, Bescon, ClearLab, Henson, INTEROJO, Laria, Gelflex."</string>
    <string name="id_356">"Orthopedic adult and children's shoes, orthopedic insoles, individual insoles, compression stockings, bandages and corsets, blood pressure monitors and glucometers, products for expectant mothers, sports and beauty, as well as rehabilitation products."</string>
    <string name="id_357">"Internet Pharmacy 36.6 - search for drugs and medical preparations in Kyiv and the region. Pharmacy chain 36.6 is one of the largest in the capital of Ukraine. Online pharmacy «Лекфарм 36.6» has a number of advantages: a large selection and a wide range, affordable prices, a simple and convenient search for medicines in the catalog, no need to stand in lines. The online pharmacy lekfarm.ua allows you to order the necessary medicines online at a convenient time."</string>
    <string name="id_358">"Internet pharmacy Receptika - a wide range of medicines at affordable prices. Online pharmacy «Рецептика» is a convenient service that allows you to choose and order medicines and other health products without leaving your home. Internet pharmacy receptika.ua offers a wide range of products, affordable prices, high level of service."</string>
    <string name="id_359">"Internet-shop «База Автозвука» - car audio, car accessories, car electronics, car goods. Leading brands - Pioneer, Alpine, Clarion, Garmin."</string>
    <string name="id_360">"Online store Dvorniki.UA offers wipers, wiper blades, Bosch, Aerotwin, Trico, Neoform, Exactfit. Delivery across Kyiv and Ukraine, the help at installation."</string>
    <string name="id_361">"«Запчасти 24» online store offers spare parts for Lanos, Tavria Slavuta, Sens, Aveo. In the online store zapchasti24.com.ua you can buy spare parts for Lanos, Tavria, Sens, Aveo with fast delivery from Zaporozhye to all cities of Ukraine, where Nova Poshta, Delivery, Justin or other delivery services operate."</string>
    <string name="id_362">"«ВСЕ ДЛЯ АВТОМОБІЛЯ» online store of auto parts and accessories. The online store is an online division of a wholesale car spare parts store in Ternopil, which has been operating in the car goods market for more than 15 years."</string>
    <string name="id_363">"Online store "120 km / h" offers automotive products, auto parts, tires. Winter, summer and all season tires for cars, car rims. Free shipping across Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_364">"TIRESHOP - Tires and Wheels online store with delivery. Sale of TIRES and DISCs in the TIRESHOP online store - low prices from suppliers, a wide range of tires and rims, delivery in Kyiv and Ukraine. Tireshop is a Ukrainian company with many years of experience in the tire business, which is the official supplier of tires and wheels of world brands in Ukraine: Michelin, GoodYear, Nokian, Hankook, Yokohama, Achilles and Rosava, and also provides services with a full range of tire services."</string>
    <string name="id_365">"The UkrClimat online store offers air conditioners, humidifiers, heaters, air purifiers, fireplaces, and also provides services for the sale and installation of air conditioners."</string>
    <string name="id_366">"The store sells household appliances, climate control equipment, metal detectors and TVs."</string>
    <string name="id_367">"«ФОРВАРД®» company specializes in the complex equipping of hotels, restaurants, cafes, bars, fast foods, supermarkets, cutting and confectionery shops with professional utensils and inventory."</string>
    <string name="id_368">"Crockery and porcelain in the online store of dishes «Мир посуды». In the World of Dishes online store you can buy dishes and kitchen utensils: porcelain, crystal, home interior products. Delivery across Kyiv and all Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_369">"The Walberry online store offers you a wide range of leather bags, wallets, clutches and other leather accessories. Leather accessories from Walberry are able to emphasize your character, style and lifestyle, and will also become your business card."</string>
    <string name="id_370">"Online store of leather bags and accessories. In the presence of women's and men's bags, briefcases, leather belts, stylish wallets and purses, purses, gift sets. Free shipping throughout Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_371">"Pet supplies, food for dogs, cats, rodents, birds and other animals. Online store «Фауна» is: a wide range of products for animals and aquariums; range of veterinary drugs and agricultural products; a network of retail pet stores in Dnepropetrovsk."</string>
    <string name="id_372">"«ПетМаркет» online pet store offers a wide range of pet products for animals, birds, fish and reptiles. The range includes: pet supplies, feed, canned food, vitamins and supplements, care and hygiene products, toys, houses, cages, toilets, beds, etc."</string>
    <string name="id_373">"Internet shop of smoking accessories. A wide range - pipes, bongs, thimbles, grinders. Delivery to all cities of Ukraine."</string>
    <string name="id_374">"Your personal intermediary in buying goods on eBay or Amazon. With our help, shopping on eBay or Amazon will be a complete pleasure for you. We have been delivering from eBay and Amazon auctions for over 4 years. We will buy and pay for the lot from ebay. Personal tracking page. No hidden fees."</string>


    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="header_menu">"You want: "</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_add">Adition</string>
    <string name="dialog_meaasge_add">Do you want to add %1$s? Press: No or Yes</string>
    <string name="add_to_favorite_shops">this shop to favorite</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_clear">Clearing ... !</string>
</resources>
